

### Email:

zardron.pesquera 1993@gmail.com

### Contact #:

+971 52 4899 398

### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/zardronangelo-pesquera-89b8961ba/

### Address:

Ras Al-Khaimah, UAE

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology University of Cebu Lapu-Lapu and Mandaue Mandaue City, Philippines

October 2017 - March 2020

# SKILLS

### Frontend

- Html
- · CSS
- Javasaript

### Backend

- · PHP
- · C#
- Javasarip t

### Frameworks:

- Laravel
- ASP.NET
- ReactJsExpressJs
- Node.ls
- Tailwind CS
- Material UI
- Material Tailwind CSS
- React Bootstrap

### Other Skills:

- Actobe Flash Player
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- hDesign
- Cisco
- MS Office
- Computer Hardware

# ZARDRON ANGELO PESQUERA

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Ambitious Web Developer with 5 years of experience in profitable companies. I lave to code because if I can think about it, I can make it a reality. Also a competitive coder with an amazing ability to develop websites that are both functional and aesthetically pleasing. I have a strong understanding of web standards and best practices, and I am passionate about creating websites that users will find easy to use and visually appealing.

# WORK HISTORY

Oct 2022 - Present

Web Developer / Marketing Executive

RAKtherm Global (Plumbing) - Full-time

Creating web application for the company using MERN Stack, designs for web applications, newsletter using Photoshop and Illustrator.

- · Designed web pages to enhance branding and navigation.
- · Managing company web applications
- Managing Repositories
- · Creating web designs
- · Designs for brochure, catalog, booklet and flyers
- Upgrading application from old technology stack to new stack
- Managing company database

Jul 2022 - Oct 2022

### ReactJs Developer

Clockwork Logistics Systems, Elk Grove California, USA

Logistics Web Application

Frontend: React.Js Backend: NacieJs Database: MongoDB

- · Create a new UI.
- · Adding new functionalities
- Refactoring existing codes
- Update some existing functionalities
- Maintain the existing web application of the company
- Managing the repository for the projects.

Jul 2021 - Jul 2022

### Software Engineer

Accenture, Celou, Central Visaryas, Philippines

Maintening Web Applications of clients using ReactJs.

- · Create a new user interface.
- · Manual Unit Testing
- · Refactor existing codes
- Fixing bugs
- Adding / Updating Functionalities.
- Managing the repository for the projects.
- Adapted to different languages and technologies based on project requirements.
- Collaborated with team members to create applications' system analyses based on client requirements.

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

## Web Develoiper

Ninety Six Back Office Operations Services, Cebu, Central Visayas, Philippines

Creating a client-based web application using react js for frontend, laravel for backend, and MySQL for the database.

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

### Web Developer

Lear Carparation, Celou, Central Visayas, Philippines

Developing a system for HR (HRMS) using ASP, NET